clicksagent.com 2017-02-20

# Privacy Policy

We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for Clicks Agent. Our site uses cookies to keep track of access information, you don't have to log in every time you enter the site. We also use cookies to track information about referred users, we pay you commission based on this information. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address). Contact information is used to send different type of notification about the system to our users. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. We do not sell, rent, loan or transfer any personal information regarding our users to any third party. Any information given us about yourself is kept with the utmost care and security and will not be used without your prior consent.

Security  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We use the latest encryption technologies and stringent limits on the number of people who have access to your information, all protect us from unauthorized access to the data.

Credit card transactions are handled by a third-party financial institution, which receives the credit card number and other personal identifying information only to verify the credit card numbers and process transactions.

Choice/Opt-Out  
Our site provides the opportunity for users to indicate the wish to not receive further communications from us, under "options" when checking out. This site gives users the the option of removal of their personal information from our database, the wish to not receive future communications or to no longer make use of our services. Please refer to "Update Account" section in the panel.

Change/Modify  
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. Please refer to "Update Account" section in the panel.

How to contact us:  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement or our web site, please use contact form.
